Hi everyone, welcome to a new blog again.
So friends, it's morning
time and I'm ready after bathing. I'm
going to visit the temple
and have to give the wiper to Pandit ji.
In the previous blog, you must have seen that we
brought the wiper from the market.
Pandit ji had asked me to bring one. The
wiper of his temple was broken, so he had asked me to get
one. We're going to
visit the temple now and will also give the wiper to Pandit ji there. Here it is,
friends. Let's
put the wiper in it. I got
down from the car and now let's go. Friends, I've put the wiper in it.
Now let's go to the temple. Friends, we've reached the temple
and now let's take out the wiper here and
give it to Pandit ji. But I
won't
make a blog about it because it won't look good if we give it. I'll make a
blog about it. Friends, I did
n't find Pandit ji in the temple. I think he has gone home. So I'm going to give it to him. The
house is near the temple. This is Pandit ji's
house. Friends, I've given the wiper to him. Now I'm going
home. So, friends, I've given the wiper to Pandit ji.
First I went to the temple but Pandit
ji wasn't found there.  So I went and gave it to his house
and we have seen the wiper, so
friends the wiper is not broken but yes it is
damaged, it was just workable now so for
now I thought you should give it to me also and at first when
Pandit ji had said it I
felt a little bad that why are you delaying but then
later when you went to give it to me I felt good so
now let's go and have breakfast
Mummy must have prepared breakfast
our breakfast is ready
[Sangeet]
Tea and here this paratha sabzi is kept we will
eat now paratha
sabzi bring the plate
[Sangeet]
what can I give it to you in small
friends I have brought breakfast and now let's sit and
eat we have eaten one paratha now we are
going to eat one more let's have breakfast now we will
meet you again after that friends yesterday I got
a message on my mobile that your
ATM card has expired so I
checked my ATM card and it was indeed
expired so I thought that now I will have to
go to the bank and apply for it
or get it enlisted it was an
ICICI Bank ATM card so I
thought that I will get it done later when I
get time so suddenly today the delivery boy  He came
and gave me my ATM card himself, I did
n't have to do anything, so this is my ATM card, so I'll get it
opened from my mother, let's
go, this is my new ATM card, and the
old one has expired, Mummy,
please
open it, open it, the ATM card has come, and the
old one has expired,
please
give it some scissors, and here I couldn't find scissors, so I'm making do
with a blade.
[Music]
Here, look, here's
my new ATM card, this one has come, the
ICICI people have sent it, the adhesive is stuck,
what should I
remove it, friends, the old one has expired, so we'll throw it away,
but
before throwing it away, we'll check once whether it's
still working or not, otherwise it must have got damaged,
and here's the new ATM
card, it looks so nice, friends, the
most fun is removing the adhesive from its back, let's
remove the adhesive, now
look at the adhesive, now this new ATM card has come to me, let's
use it, and the old
one will be thrown away, see what Mummy is doing with
it, what will you do with it, now you take it away, take it away,
friends, Mummy is cutting the
watermelon, let it be cut,
after that we'll show you the
seeds in it.  They come and it is the most
difficult to take them out and I am going to
eat it now, if it does
not have a red sheet and a red watermelon plate then it will not be known.